https://challengecancer.com/privacy-policy/

Anonymous Data Collection and Use
To maintain this website’s high quality, Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell, may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site by identifying which areas of the website are most heavily used and to display content according to your preferences. Your IP address is the number assigned to computers connected to the Internet. This is essentially “traffic data” which cannot personally identify you, but is helpful to Challengecancer.com for marketing purposes and for improving our services. Traffic data collection does not follow a user’s activities on any other websites in any way. Anonymous traffic data may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate basis.
Submission and Sharing of Personal Data
Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell, may seek personal data including your name, e-mail address, and other contact information, namely when you take actions such as subscribe to our newsletter, join our private forum(s), comment on our blog, or contact us. This information is used to contact the user about the program or information for which they have expressed interest. There may be an occasion where we may ask for demographic information such as gender and age, to personalize our programs or correspondence, or to distinguish adults from minors, but if you choose not to provide such personally identifiable data and information, you may still use the website, but will not be able to use services if such information may be required.
Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell, may share personal data and information about our visitors with reliable select business partners and other third parties. Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell, will not otherwise share your personal data and identifying information without your consent, except as necessary when the law requires it or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary, particularly when disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to others or interfering with Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell’s rights or property.
Note that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online, such as on blogs, message boards, emails, or in chat areas – the information you share also can be seen, collected and used by third parties, and therefore, we cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third party use of such information that you voluntarily share.
Passwords
By using Challengecancer.com’s website you agree to enter true and accurate information on the site as a part of the registration process. It is your responsibility to protect your own password from disclosure to others. You are responsible for activities that take place using your password and within your account. If you share your password with anyone, they may be able to obtain access to your personal information. If you enter a bogus email address we have the right to immediately deactivate your account.
Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell, will use its best efforts to keep your passwords private and will not otherwise share your passwords without your consent, except as necessary when the law requires it or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary, particularly when disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to others or interfering with Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell’s rights or property.
Anti-Spam Policy
Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell has a no spam policy and provides you with the ability to opt-out of our communications by selecting the unsubscribe link at the footer of all e-mails. Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell will not sell, rent or share your email address.
Unsubscribe
You may unsubscribe to any blogs, newsletters, social media page or Program or Service of  Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell at any time through the unsubscribe link provided in various communications and on the Membership Site account page. Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell manages e-mail lists through a list management system. Unsubscribing from one list managed by Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell  will not necessarily remove the user from all publication email lists. Users with questions or experiencing problems unsubscribing should contact us at info@challengecancer.com.
Use of “Cookies”
Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell may use the standard “cookies” feature of major web browsers. Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your computer that contains information about the user. Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell does not set any personally identifiable information in cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of our website are useful and which areas need improvement. You may choose to disable cookies through your web browser’s settings. However, disabling this function may diminish your experience on the website and some features may not work as intended. Cookie information is only used when communicating with users as per their indicated preferences and as needed for service-related communications. Third party content that may be displayed on our site may also contain its own cookies, but Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell has no access to or control over any information collected by third parties through the website.
Third Party Links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites, and therefore we cannot be held liable for the information on their website or that you voluntarily share with their website. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and we welcome any feedback about these websites.
Assignment of Rights
In the event of an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer of some or all of  Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell’s assets, you agree Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell can assign, sell, license or transfer any information that you have provided to us. Please note, however, that the purchasing party cannot use the personal data and information submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.
Notification of Changes
Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell may use your contact information to inform you of changes to the website, or, if requested, to send you additional information about Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell. Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell’s reserve the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes and/or modifications shall become effective immediately upon the posting thereof.  Please review this Privacy Policy periodically. Continued use of any Challengecancer.com, NutriQuest Press, LLC, NutriQuest, Inc. or Dr Kim Dalzell programs or information obtained through or on the website following the posting of changes and/or modifications constitutes acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy.
